The Apocalypse is a action, science fiction film directed by Justin Jones.
A mother and a father search for their only child as a giant asteroid
headed for Earth, triggering a series of apocalyptic events.
Jason, played by Rhett Giles.
Ashley, played by Jill Stapley.
Lindsay, played by Kristen Quintrall.
Andrew, played by Tom Nagel.
Don, played by David Shick.
Khalil, played by Amol Shah.
The Asylum is an American independent film company and distributor that
focuses on producing low-budget, direct-to-video films.
The company has produced titles that capitalize on productions by major studios, often using film titles
and scripts very similar to those of current blockbusters in order to lure customers.
These titles have been dubbed "mockbusters" by the press.
The tone is thought_provoking.